

# LYNN TSAI

Graphic & Web Designer Motion Graphics Animator Illustrator



## CONTACT



#### Website

https://tsaichialin.com/portfolio



#### Email

chialin.tsai@gmail.com



#### **Phone**

0918477326



#### Linkedin

https://linkedin.com/in/tsaichialin

## SKILLS

## **Graphic & Print Design**

- Phtoshop Illustrator
- InDesign

#### Website

- Figma Adobe XD
- HTML CSS SCSS RWD Git
- Google Web Designer
- WordPress

# **Motion Graphics**

• After Effects • Lottie

## **Video Shooting & Editing**

- Premiere
- Audition

# **EDUCATION**

MA in Multimedia and Animation Art National Taiwan University of Arts 2000-2003

#### **BA in Arts and Education**

National Taipei University of Education 1995-1999

# PROFILE

Lynn Tsai (Chia-lin Tsai), self-driven design professional with 17 years of experience. Enthusiastic designer with solid problem solving skills. Solid understanding of branding, typography, print and motion graphics. Created and designed eye-catching visual content, such as book, flyer, brochure, website, animation, banner, video, and social media post.

I'm working for a global Fintech company, collaborated with marketing and design team, able to adapt to a fast-paced multinational environment.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Digital Designer**

ZeroLogix 2021 - Present

Zerologix is a Fintech company from Austratralia, my duties included:

- Crafted 100+ video assets for our YouTube channel and Instagram.
- Promotional materials social media posts, banner Ads, exhibition design.
- Created print materials, such as posters, flyers, banner ads and brochures.
- Designed company letterhead, presentation template, used regularly by people within the company.

## Web Designer

BFM 2019 - 2021

In the advertising agency, my duties included:

- Create website layout and user interface using HTML/CSS/JS, troubleshooting issues across desktop and mobile devices.
- Promotional materials for printed, Google Display Network, banner Ads.
- Create custom websites using WordPress.
- Create graphics and animations for YouTube, Facebook videos.

#### **Art Director**

A Blissful Moment 2018 - 2019

- Present concepts and design guidelines to animation team, leading projects from concept through to completion.
- Collaborated with concept designers and animators, ensuring that all requirments to meet director needs.

# **Concept Designer**

Gamania Digital Entertainment 2005 - 2017

- Tell stories through animation, motion graphics, and video editing.
- · Create graphics and animations for TV series and short films.
- · Website content / Social Media management.

# **Graphic Designer**

XFUNS Creative Magazine 2003 - 2004

Create magazine layout designs and promotional materials.